All units, all units. Code 3 pursuit of 2- 11.
各小組鳴笛追捕罪犯，有空中支援
White SUV heading east on Alameda service road.
白色SUV車在阿拉米達輔路向東逃竄
Suspects: Three Asian males.
嫌犯是3名亞洲男子
HANCOCK
全民超人漢考克
Be advised. Shots fired, shots fired.
大家注意，已經交火
Hancock!
漢考克！
What, boy?
干嘛，小子？
Bad guys.
有坏人啊
What, you want a cookie? Get out of my face.
想找餅干吃？從我眼前滾開
Asshole.
混蛋
- What? - You heard me.
- 你說我啥？ - 你听到了
Asshole.
混蛋
Watch out!
快閃開！
Damn!
靠！
Damn it!
該死！
Hancock!?!
漢考克？！
Beat it, 'Soulja Boy! '
扁他，“醬爆弟弟”！
He smells like a bar!
他一身酒气
You pay for new roof!
你賠我們新車頂！
Fellas, hey. I don't give a shit what you did. I don't care.
伙計們，我才不管你們干了什么
Three guys in the car, no girls, rave music.
仨老爺們儿呆在車里面 沒妞陪著，音樂這么爛
Hey, I'm not gonna judge.
我就不說啥了
But if you don't pull over and give yourselves up quietly...
可你們要是不乖乖停車投降
...I swear to Christ, your head is going up the driver's ass.
我對天發誓，把你腦袋塞進司机的屁股里
His head is going up your ass. And you drew the short stick...
他腦袋進你屁股里，而你最倒霉
...because your head is going up my ass.
因為你腦袋要進我屁股里
Shoot this asshole!
打死這混蛋！
Stop!
別開槍了！
What the F%*#K?
這他媽的是怎么回事？
こんにちは(Konnichiwa)
你們好（日語）
What? I'm not Japanese, man!
大哥！我又不是日本人
Put us down!
放我們下來啊！
Oh, now you "speaky Engly," huh? "Speaky Engly" now?
現在小嘴儿會說英語啦？
You broke my glasses.
我眼鏡打坏了
I'm sorry! Take my Ray-Bans!
對不起啊！把我的雷邦眼鏡拿走！
- Put us down! - You want down?
- 把我們放下來！ - 想要下來了？
- Yes, please! Please! - Help me!
- 是啊，求求你！ - 救命啊！
I'm real good at down.
我的下落水平可是一流啊
All right? All right.
怎么樣？來吧
This, Hancock's latest act of so-called heroics...
這就是漢考克最新的所謂壯舉
...took a hefty financial toll.
造成的巨額經濟損失
Initial damage estimates are said to top $9 million...
初步估計達9百万美元
...which, if accurate...
如果數字准确…
...represents a personal record...
對于臭名昭著處事低調的他
...for the notoriously publicity-shy Hancock...
倒是刷新了個人紀錄
...who, as usual, can't be reached for comment.
和以前一樣，他對此拒絕評論
With all the cracks to the concrete, all the bullets, water damage, fires...
水泥路損坏、子彈亂飛加上水災火災
...L.A. Would be better off if this guy would leave...
要是沒有這家伙給我們添亂
...and let us get on with our jobs.
洛杉磯市會更和諧
Hi.
嗨
Don't think I'm crazy, okay? We've looked everywhere for you.
別認為我瘋了，行嗎？我們到處找你
Going to the Roxy and the Viper Room and Jumbo's...
去過羅克希劇院、蛇窩夜總會、君勃酒吧
...anywhere we thought you would be at. I found you.
能想到的都找過了，我總算找著你了
I got you.
我抓找你啦
So, what's it like when you fly?
你飛的時候是什么樣？
- No, what? - I ain't gonna fly you.
- 什么不行？ - 我不會帶你飛的
I got a cousin, Narelle. She's my best friend in the entire world...
我表妹叫納讓，是我最好的朋友
...and I swear to God she would not be here today if it wasn't for you.
我發誓，沒有你，她肯定今天活不了
She crashed her car up in Malibu and you flew her to the hospital.
她在馬里步市出了車禍 你飛著送到了醫院
Remember?
沒忘了吧？
I will break my foot off in your ass, woman.
再盯著我，我就把腳踢進你屁股里，大姐
You got a car?
你有車嗎？
Hey, want a drink?
想喝點什么？
So this is where you live. This is your hideout.
原來你就住這儿，你隱居的小窩
Your Batcave.
像蝙蝠俠的指揮部
Your Fortress of Solitude.
超人的總部
- It's a couple trailers I stuck together. - What's all this?
- 這房子是我把兩個拖車接一起弄的 - 這些是什么？
- Jiffy Pop.
- 即飛爆米花
- What do you do with it? - Pop it.
- 你一般怎么弄熟呢？ - 把它爆熟
Jiffy Pop, pop. I like that.
即飛爆米花，听著就勁爆，我喜歡
Hold on.
等一下
Want me to give you something else to pop?
我再給你點什么讓你爆，想要嗎？
- I didn't catch your name. - Pop this, Superman.
- 我沒听清你名字 - 讓我爆吧，超人
Not much for the chitchat, huh? Let me set this over here.
不聊聊就來干脆的？讓我先把這個放好
- All right. Now, there are some rules. - Hello?
- 好了，先跟你說點規矩 - 喂？
- No, I know, I haven't seen it yet. - Excuse me.
- 我知道，還沒見到呢 - 先讓一下
I know, probably. All right, all right.
是啊，有可能，就先這樣
- Let me call you back. - Listen.
- 回頭打電話給你 - 听好了
You're gonna need to focus. All right, I need you...
你需要注意點，好吧，我要你…
- Hey, that's... That's not focusing. - What's in there?
- 不是這樣… - 我想看你那里
Okay, all right, hold on. Stop. Stop it. All right, now...
先等等，停下，好了
...when I get to the moment... - The moment?
- 當我到了那個時候 - 那個時候？
You know, the... Start climbing the mountaintop, you know?
嗯，就是我“到山頂”了
- You know... All right? Yes. - Yeah.
- 明白吧？好吧 - 明白
You're gonna need to be as far away from that as possible.
那時候你得盡量躲遠點
- Far. That's hot. - No, that's not hot. It's not hot.
- 遠點，好性感 - 不，這可不性感
- Oh, yeah. - Okay.
- 行啊 - 好的
Hancock. Oh, yeah.
漢考克
- Now you're doing too much. - Hancock.
- 你已經過頭了 - 漢考克
Oh, mountaintop! Mountaintop!
到頂了！頂天了！
Mountaintop! Watch out!
衝天了！小心！
Sorry.
很抱歉
That's not fair to anybody.
像那樣對誰都不太好
Thank you for being okay with that.
謝謝你接受這點
- I know it's... - Can I use the bathroom, please?
- 這确實有點… - 我能用下廁所嗎？
Yeah. Hey, you...? You want some Jiffy Pop?
好啊，你…你想要點爆米花嗎？
- No, thanks. - It's straight back.
- 不用了 - 馬上就能好
- You all right? - Yeah.
- 你沒事儿吧？ - 沒事
Yeah, I was trying to tell you.
我本想跟你說的就是這個
Hey...
嘿
Listen... You know, if you want I could fly you.
你想飛的話我可以帶你飛
It's really beautiful, you know? Earth.
很漂亮的，整個地球
You could see the...
你都能看見…
Might have to get you a helmet, so your face doesn't tear off.
可能得給你罩個頭盔，要不臉保不住
What do you think?
你覺得怎么樣？
Sir? Ray Embrey.
先生，這是瑞•安伯雷
Ray's like the Bono of P.R.
他就像公關界的歌手波諾一樣
Well, actually, I think Bono is the Bono of P.R., but I do try.
其實波諾他自己才名副其實，我會盡力
Well, let's see it.
呵呵，我們拭目以待
Okay. I'll get right into it. Good morning, everyone.
好的，馬上開始，大家早上好
I'm here to talk to you about charitable giving.
我想跟大家談一談慈善捐助
Okay? And we all know the way that works.
通常來講
You give one, maybe two percent of your net cash...
你們捐出純收入的1%或2%
and you get an armband or a ribbon or whatever. It's nowhere near enough.
得到個臂章、絲帶什么的 不過這些捐助遠遠不夠
And that's why we at Embrey Publicity would like to offer you...
正因如此，我們安伯雷公關公司為您
...the AllHeart symbol.
提供新的“全心全意”標志
Now, you would be among a very select group of corporate giants...
使用它的大型公司都是我們精心挑選的
...to bear this logo on your product.
你們也可以把它印到商品上
And what this would say to the public...
這相當于告訴公眾
...is that your company, Pharmatopsis...
你們尖峰制藥公司
...has made a radical contribution to helping our world.
為拯救世界做出了杰出貢獻
Here's all you need to do to qualify.
而你們只要這么做就行
Your new TB drug, Mycodin?
你們有肺結核的新藥麥克定吧？
We would like for you to give that product away for free.
我們希望你們能免費提供給病人
- Did you say "free"? - I did.
- 你剛才說免費？ - 是的
Only to those who need it.
只給真正需要的人
Only to those who without it would otherwise die.
只給那些沒有它就活不了的
As a concept, free is kind of up there with, you know, lethal side effects.
免費提供我們的產品會讓人誤以為藥物有副作用
- Mandatory product recall. - Get indicted, go to jail.
- 完了強行回收 - 上法庭，進監獄
Get out, work at IHOP for the rest of your career.
毀了自己一生的職業生涯
Understandable reaction. It's a radical concept.
你們的反應我能理解，這种理念确實激進，但…
But it is the brand that represents a fairer and better world.
這個標志代表著更美好的世界
The brand...
這個標志…
...that everyone is talking about.
是現在大家的熱門話題
Who is "everyone"?
大家指誰？
We do already have a sports franchise.
我們已經獲得一個体育專營權
- NFL? NBA? MLB? - Soccer.
- 國家橄欖球聯盟？NBA？棒球？ - 是足球
MLS? Which team?
美國職業足球聯盟？哪個隊？
Well, it's a local team. Encino Hurricanes.
哦，是本地球隊，“茵西諾颶風”隊
It's my son's team.
我儿子的球隊
Anyway, we can save the world.
總之呢，我們這樣就能拯救世界
All right? Someone's just gotta go first.
總要有第一個吃螃蟹的人
What do you say?
你們意下如何？
Are you a crackpot?
你腦子進水了？
Hey, hon. You're probably at the store. I am on my way.
親愛的，你可能還在商店里 我在回去的路上
I think I made a connection.
估計能跟他們日后合作
Not really.
其實沒戲
Listen, tell Aaron that I'm coming and l... Damn it.
告訴艾倫我就回去…糟糕
And I want some meatballs, okay?
做點肉丸子好嗎？
I need some Spaghetti Madness. I'll see you in about 20 minutes.
今天輪到超級意大利面了 20分鐘后見
Hey! What is it, National Horn Day?
急什么急？又不是全國鳴笛日
Idiot.
白痴
Hey.
嘿
Hey. Hey!
嘿，嘿！
Move it. There's a train coming.
快開車，火車要過來了
Do you not hear that horn?
沒听見喇叭響？
Let's go! I got a train!
快動啊！火車過來了
Move it!
開車啊！
- Back your car up! There's a train! - I can't go anywhere. Get out!
- 快倒車！有火車！ - 我也卡住了，下車吧！
Son of a bitch!
見鬼！
Fix the handle, Ray. Fix the handle.
我該修門把手了
Get out!
下來啊！
Get off the track! Move!
從鐵軌上躲開！快點！
- Somebody help him. - You all right?
你還好嗎？
You sure?
真沒事？
- Ah, shit. - I'm all right. I'm okay.
- 唉，該死 - 我沒事，沒受傷
All of you people...
你們這些人
...blocking the intersection...
擋在十字路口上的
...you're all idiots.
你們都是白痴
You threw the dude's car at her. And what's with the train?
是你先把車砸向她的，還有這火車
Why didn't you just go straight up in the air with the car?
你干嘛不把車提到天上去啊？
You've obviously injured that poor woman.
你肯定把那可怜的女人傷著了
- She's right. She should sue you. - Yeah, she should sue you.
- 她說得對，就該起訴你 - 是啊，她就該起訴你
Well, you should sue McDonald's because they fucked you up.
你該去告麥當勞，把你養成豬了
You're an asshole.
你真是個混蛋
And I can smell that liquor on your breath.
我都能聞見酒味了
- Because I've been drinking, bitch. - You're a drunk asshole!
- 因為我剛喝著酒，小潑婦 - 你是個酒鬼混蛋！
- You think you're such a hero. - Asshole!
- 自以為是什么大英雄 - 混蛋！
- You're nothing but an asshole. - We don't need you in this city.
- 徹頭徹尾的混蛋！ - 我們可不需要你
Some superhero you are! Fly off!
就你這破英雄！快飛一邊去吧
Shut up!
都別說了！
Don't you understand? I'm alive.
你們沒看到我還活著嗎？
I get to go home and see my family. I should be dead right now, right here.
我還能回去見家人，剛才差點就死在這了
Yeah, he could've gone straight up. Obviously, you should've.
他當然可以把車提起來，也該那樣
You know, and I was upside down for the train, but...
我在車里可是頭朝下，不過…
No. Thank you.
不管怎樣，謝謝你
Thank you very much, Hancock. Thank you.
非常感謝，漢考克，謝謝你
Thank you, Hancock.
謝謝，漢考克
You're not flying by the Valley, are you?
你能順便帶我到山谷區那邊嗎？
Throw the ball!
把球扔過來
Monte, one guy'll line up here, all right? Hike the ball.
蒙迪，它在這列好隊 好了？猛地踢球
This guy'll be right here and he says, "Hut!"
另一個在這儿大喝一聲
This guy'll drop back. Hut! Drop back. Chuck it.
他倆完了后退，球扔了過來
Great. Thank you.
好极了，謝謝你
Nice aim. The driveway would've been better, but...
挺准的，雖說放車道上更好些
- What's going on, Dad? - Hey, buddy.
- 爸爸怎么了？ - 小伙子
Daddy's had a little bit of a day. Look at you, huh?
我這一天可是十分夠勁儿
I want you to meet somebody.
來見見這個人
This guy here, dragging Daddy's car into the driveway.
就是把車拉到車道上這個
- Who's this? - Hancock.
- 這是誰呀？ - 漢考克
That's right. Hancock, this is my boy, Aaron.
是他，漢考克，這是我儿子艾倫
- Ray, what happened to the car? - Oh, boy.
- 瑞，車是怎么回事？ - 天哪
You would not have believed it.
說了你也不信
I came this close to getting hit by a train. If it wasn't for that guy...
火車就差這么一點撞死我，要不是他…
He saved my life. I mean... Hancock, this is my wife, Mary.
漢考克救了我，這是我妻子瑪麗
Believe that? I almost kissed a train.
你信不？火車差點親死我
Saw my whole life flash before my eyes.
這一輩子都在我眼前閃過
- He saved your life? - He sure did. Thank you.
- 他救了你？ - 是他，謝謝
- Hey, you good? - I am good, yeah.
- 你還好嗎？ - 我還行
- All right. Keep it off the tracks. - I will, definitely.
- 下次离鐵軌遠點 - 我肯定會小心的
Hang on a... One second.
等一下
- Hancock, you eat, yes? Human food? - Yeah.
- 漢考克，你吃東西吧？人類食物？ - 嗯
- You like meatballs? - No.
- 喜歡吃肉丸子嗎？ - 儿子，不行
Aaron, sweetheart, he has to go and do...
親愛的艾倫，他還要去忙…
I love meatballs.
我喜歡吃丸子
Who's so busy they can't have a meal?
誰會忙得連飯都吃不上？
And it's on us. Please.
我們請客
I'm not even gonna take no for an answer. Get inside the house.
別讓了，進屋吧
Why do you have an eagle on your hat?
為什么你帽子上有只老鷹？
Do you like eagles?
你喜歡老鷹嗎？
This guy's like a little talking machine, huh?
小家伙挺愛說的嘛
We don't have a lot of guests over here.
平時我們客人不多
Look at that, huh? Hon, is the heat on?
看看這多好，火還開著嗎？
No? All right.
關了？好
We started Spaghetti Madness about two years ago.
兩年前我們開始做超級意大利面
We do it every Thursday, and we have not missed a Thursday in...
每個星期四都吃，一次沒落下過
- Ever. - Yeah.
- 從來沒有 - 是啊
- Ever? That's a long time. - Yes, sir.
- 從沒落下過？這可有歷史了
- A very long time. - That's some good meatballs, boy.
- 挺長時間了 - 小子，丸子很好吃
Aaron.
艾倫
- Your mama's calling you. - Yes, Mom?
- 你媽媽喊你 - 怎么了，媽媽
No. His name is Aaron.
沒事，我是說他叫艾倫
- Hey, Aaron, how was school today? - Fine.
- 艾倫，今天在學校過得怎么樣？ - 挺好的
Yeah? No more problems with that bully, Michael?
霸道的麥克沒欺負你吧？
- Michel. But not like a girl's name. - Michel. No, no, I know.
- 他叫米歇爾，但不是女孩名字 - 我知道
- It's French. - Yeah. Michel, Hancock, is this...
- 是法語名字 - 這個米歇爾…
Hancock? Michel is this neighborhood bully.
漢考克，他是個隔壁的小惡霸
We've been trying to teach Aaron a little...
我們告訴過艾倫
...about conflict resolution. You know what I mean?
教過他一些解決衝突的辦法，你知道的
- Yeah. Turn the other cheek, all that? - That's exactly right.
- 大度忍讓那种？ - 是啊
Well, just never turn that one, all right?
記住，不能等著屁股挨踢
Never let them punk you.
不能讓他打你
- Got it, Mr. Hancock. - Aaron, eat.
- 明白了，漢考克 - 艾倫，吃飯
The way you deal with bullies, you take your right foot...
對付惡霸的方法，就是抬起你的右腳
...bring it right up and catch him in his little piss pump.
照著他小雞雞踢過去
You don't have to do that, honey, okay? Seriously.
你不用非得這樣，听著了嗎？
It's a good idea.
這主意挺好
You aim straight and make sure he can't use that thing...
你得踢准了
...for nothing but a flap to keep the dust out of his butt crack.
一腳把他雞雞踢成給屁股擋風的小旗子
Okay, please, just stop.
行了，別說了
Michel is not a man, okay?
米歇爾還沒成年
He's a little boy. And his parents...
只是個小孩
...happen to be going through a bad divorce. That's why he's acting up.
爸媽正鬧离婚，所以他才耍脾气
Maybe you don't know this...
也許你不了解情況
...but not everything in this world gets resolved with force.
但這個世上不是什么事儿都要靠暴力解決
- Not everything has to be bang... - I'm set.
- 不是非要橫衝直撞 - 這些夠了
...scream, blood, more blood. - Baby, I got plenty. Angel! We're okay.
- …弄得頭破血流，讓更多人受罪 - 小天使，這些就夠了！
She watches so much news...
她新聞看太多了
...that sometimes it gets to be a little too much.
可能有點承受不了
- You got a toilet? - Yep. Yeah, just past the fridge.
- 有廁所嗎？ - 走過冰箱就是
Did he just take the whiskey bottle to the bathroom?
他是不是剛才拿酒瓶去的廁所？
Do you want him to kill us all?
你想讓他一气之下把咱們全殺了？
Thanks for coming on in. Good, right?
謝謝你過來，還行吧？
- Very, yeah. - Wanna say goodbye to him?
- 很不錯 - 你也說再見
- Bye, Hancock. - Hey, all right, little buddy.
- 再見，漢考克 - 好的，小家伙
- Are you okay? - It was a joke.
- 你沒事吧？ - 開個玩笑
- Come on, Aaron. - Hey, sorry. I was just trying to...
- 過來，艾倫 - 抱歉，我只是想…
He got it. She didn't get it.
小伙明白了，她沒有
I owe you. You gave me my life back today.
我欠你個人情，你今天救了我的命
Hear me out. I'd like to return the favor.
听我說，我想報答你
Do you know what I do? I'm in public relations.
知道我做什么嗎？我是公關
You know what that is? Of course you do. We're image consultants.
也就是形象顧問
We change the way people see products, companies,people, that stuff.
我們能改變人們的看法 不管對產品、公司，還是人
Listen, I see you on the news and I see you out there today...
我今天在新聞上看到你了
...and it can't feel good that people, you know, hate you.
人們討厭你，你肯定也不好受
- It's good to meet you, Ray. - No, I'm sorry.
- 見到你很高興 - 別生气啊
But hear me out.
請讓我說完
People... Don't get me wrong, they should love you. They really should.
別誤會我，人們其實應該喜歡你，真的
I wanna deliver that for you. It's the least that I can do.
我想要幫你，我就是干這行的
You know, you're a superhero.
你是個超級英雄
Kids should ask you for your autograph.
孩子們應該爭著要你簽名
People should cheer you on the streets.
街上的人們應該為你歡呼
What the hell are you pricks looking at?
你們這幫家伙瞎看什么！
No, no, they're not... It's all right.
他們沒看…沒關系的
They're not pricks, they're just people.
他們沒惡意，就是普通人
But I want you to give me one short pitch, you know?
回頭找我簡單聊聊
That's all I ask. Okay?
我就這點要求了，行嗎？
You use...
這個…
Put it under here?
放這下面？
Put it right there. Perfect.
放這儿挺好的
E-mail me or whatever. You just fly on over, I don't know.
發郵件之類的聯系我，飛過來也行
I want you to think about it.
希望你考慮一下
Just be careful when you go. Sleep on it, all right?
回去路上看著點，這事明天再說
You get back to me?
你會找我吧？
I'll be right here. All right.
我就在這儿等著
Please don't stare, you guys. He's kind of one of us.
大伙別看了，他跟咱們一樣
What about AllHeart?
你那計划怎么樣了？
It's a nonstarter, babe, you know? I'm chasing windmills with that.
沒啥希望，白忙活了
Maybe I can't change the world but I can change this guy's life.
我可能改變不了世界，但能改變他的生活
- Think about all the good he can do. - I think you're wasting your time.
- 想一想他能做的好事 - 我想你在浪費時間
You really hate him.
你還真討厭他啊
Hate? I don't hate him, Ray. I don't even know the guy.
討厭？我都不了解他怎么討厭他？
Just look at the news. You can see what he does.
看看新聞吧，看看他做的事
I think he just needs people to care, you know?
我想他可能缺少別人的關心
You see the good in everybody, Ray.
你總看人好的一面
Even sometimes when it's not there.
甚至有時优點根本就不存在，你也如此
I have a feeling about this. Don't work with this guy.
我有不好的預感，別跟他合作
I know this kind of guy. He breaks things.
這种人只會把東西搞砸
Frankenstein
《科學怪人》電影票
My bad. Everybody all right?
怪我不好，大家沒事吧？
I'll go and get my mommy.
找我媽媽去
He is an asshole.
他真是個混蛋
- What's your name, boy? - Michel.
- 你叫啥，小子？ - 米歇爾
- You know who I am? - My papa says you are an asshole.
- 知道我是誰嗎？ - 我爸說你是個混蛋
Well, that's not really a nice word to call a person, is it?
這么說別人可不算好話啊
- Asshole? - Yeah.
- 叫人混蛋？ - 是啊
Because that could make someone very angry...
這樣會把人惹毛了
...and, you know, maybe hurt their feelings.
還讓人心情不爽
You behave like an asshole.
可你的舉止就像個混蛋
All right...
得了…
Do you know Aaron?
你認識艾倫嗎？
Wee, la petit asshole.
就那個小混蛋（法語）
Well, seems to be a pretty good kid.
嗯，他其實是個好孩子
Just wanna ask you to lay off of him a little bit.
我想讓你离他遠點
Why, asshole?
為什么？混蛋？
- You're gonna stop calling me that. - Asshole.
- 你別這么叫我了 - 混蛋
- That's not my name.
- 我不叫這名儿
Call me a asshole...
你有本事…
...one more time.
再說一遍
Asshole.
混蛋
How about you, thickness?
你也試試，小胖？
Goggles?
你呢，四眼？
Hancock! You son of a gun, I knew you'd come.
漢考克，你這家伙，我就知道你會來
Ask Mary. I had a feeling.
不信問瑪麗，我猜對了
I said, he heard me and he's ready for a change.
你听進去了，确實想要改變自己
This is great. Did you do this? You come in a little hot?
太好了，來的路上挺熱的吧？
I'll meet you in the house.
屋里見
- I know you don't drive, but... - Oh, damn it, Ray.
- 我知道你不開車… - 該死
All right. You're all right. You're all right. You're all right.
你沒事了，沒事了
Oh, stop crying, punk-ass. Go ahead.
別哭了，臭小子，回去吧
- Not okay. Okay? - He all right.
- 你這可不好啊 - 他沒事儿的
Really not okay. This is some of the stuff we're gonna work on.
真的不太好，我得幫你改改
How do you think that conversation's gonna go down with his mom?
要是他跟你一樣，就這么砸在馬路中間
Landing like that in the street's also on the uncool side.
怎么和他媽媽交待？
No, that was already like that when I got here, Ray.
我來之前馬路就這樣了
I live here. I know what the street's like.
我住這儿，我知道馬路什么樣
We'll make those problems of the past.
我們得解決你之前的那些問題
I'm gonna teach you how to interface with the public.
教給你怎么和公眾打交道
- Where's the wife? - Mary took Aaron to his soccer game.
- 你妻子呢？ - 她帶艾倫去踢足球了
Hancock, pulled some stuff up on YouTube.
漢考克，我在Youtube上找了點東西
Surprisingly large amount of not-great stuff on you that's gonna be helpful.
你的負面新聞可真不少啊 不過對我們有幫助
What is this?
這是什么？
That's me trying to change the world.
我想用這個改變世界
Unfortunately, not doing real well.
不過不太順利
Come on. Let's get to you.
過來，看看你吧
This stuff was on YouTube.
這是在Youtube上的
Everybody loves a Nutty Buddy, I get it, but this doesn't work, sir.
大家都愛吃冰激凌， 可也不能這么搶啊，老兄
Hey, give me a Nutty Buddy. Back up, back up.
給我個冰激凌，你們后退點
Mom! Mom! Mom!
媽媽，媽媽！
Those are children.
這是當著小孩的面啊
- We've been waiting a long time... - Get that camera out of my face.
- 我們排隊這么久了… - 別拿鏡頭對著我
You ever put out an apartment fire, Ray?
瑞，你救過公寓大火嗎？
- No, I haven't done that. I'm in P.R. - No. My ass was hot.
- 沒有，我是干公關的 - 把我屁股都烤著了
All right. How about this? This is Walter, the gray whale.
好吧，那這個呢？叫瓦爾特的灰鯨魚
Everybody remembers him stuck on the beach north of Zuma.
大家都記得它困在祖瑪海灘上了
Along comes Hancock.
你來了
Hancock!
漢考克！
- I don't even remember that. - Yeah.
- 我都不記得了 - 是啊
Greenpeace does. Walter does.
綠色和平組織還沒忘，鯨魚也是
This gets redundant after a while...
不過這些大家會忘記的
...but my basic diagnosis of your fundamental problem is...
其實我覺得你問題的根源是…
- Do you wanna hear it? - No.
- 想听嗎？ - 不想
You're an asshole.
你是個混蛋
I know. I call it like I see it though.
雖然不中听，可我有啥說啥
It's not a crime to be an asshole but it's counterproductive.
做混蛋不是犯罪，可沒好處
But you are an asshole, don't you think?
你不否認你是個混蛋吧？
Be careful.
說話小心點
All right, how about this? I've been thinking about something.
好吧，听听這個，我一直在想
This kind of goes to how you present yourself.
這些都能歸結到你怎么展示自己
Come on. Really? It's the middle of the day. What springs to mind...
真是的，才中午喝什么酒
...when you see this?
看這個，你腦子里想到什么？
Homo.
同性戀
- What about that? - Homo in red.
- 這個呢？ - 紅衣服同性戀
- Norwegian homo. - I'll give you that.
- 挪威同性戀 - 算了算了
Let's move past the comics. Let's get into something a little deeper.
放下漫畫，咱們深入討論一點
I think that deep down you behave badly because you're lonely.
我覺得你因為孤獨才行為惡劣
I think deep down, you want people's acceptance.
心底里還是想要人們接受自己的
Come on, now. You save people's lives...
得啦，你救了人命
...and they reject you, and so you reject them back.
人們卻排斥你，所以你也排斥他們
And it's a... And we're gonna switch that cycle.
然后就…咱們得改變這個惡性循環
We're gonna start fresh, start anew.
我們得從新開始
This is outstanding. If you turn some of this power into willpower...
你力气真大，你要是轉移到意志力上…
- And then he kicked it in. - Almost.
- 然后他就射進門了 - 就差一點
Hey, Hancock! We almost won.
漢考克！我們差點就贏了
Yeah, we did. Okay, upstairs. I'm making lunch. Go change.
是啊，上樓去換衣服，我去做午飯
Hey, sweetheart.
嘿，甜心
Have you been watching the news?
看新聞了嗎？
- No, we've been working on... - Interfacing with the public.
- 沒有，我們正在練習… - 和公眾打交道
- This has been on all day. - That's very good.
電視上都放了一天了
The law is the law, Mr. Hancock, and you are not above it.
法律就是法律，漢考克先生 你也不能凌駕于法律之上
Felony destruction of property...
破坏公共財產…
...amounting to tens of millions of dollars, theft, and now this.
上千万的損失，盜竊，現在又來這個
From where I sit, I see a selfish, self-absorbed man...
我只看到一個自私自利的人
...with a lot of muscle, but no regard for anyone but yourself.
空有一身肌肉，完全不尊重他人
Mr. Hancock, let me remind you.
漢考克先生，我告訴你
You are not above the law.
你也不能凌駕于法律之上
You have failed to show at over 600 subpoenas in civil suits.
600多次民事傳訊你都不來
Anybody else would be held in contempt. But, oh, no. Not you.
換別人早沒臉見人了，而你不一樣
You may be a superhero, but let me tell you this:
你是有點本事，可我告訴你
You're not nearly as strong as the U.S. Constitution.
你對抗不了美國憲法
Bank on it, buddy.
有本事試試看，老兄
We do not condone the t...
我們絕不容忍…
Genius.
我真是天才
Things just got real. This is exactly what we need.
剛想到就成真了，咱們就缺這個
There's a DA trying to figure out how to put you in jail.
地方檢察官要把你關進監獄
- Bitch can try. - I say you go.
- 這賤人敢惹我試試 - 你應該將計就計
People take you for granted. Make people miss you.
欲擒故縱，讓他們想念你
- People don't like you, Hancock. - I do.
- 人們不喜歡你，漢考克 - 可我喜歡
Two weeks, you know? The public will be clamoring for you.
只要兩個星期，他們就會吵著讓你回來
When they do, we'll be ready.
等他們這么做了，時机就成熟了
Worst-case scenario is I'm wrong and you just, you know, fly out of there.
最坏也就是我判斷失誤 你也能輕松越獄
What do you got to lose?
你也沒啥損失
"I apologize to the people of Los Angeles.
我向洛杉磯市的人民道歉
My behavior has been improper, and I accept the consequences.
我為我魯莽行為承擔后果
I ask my fellow Angelenos...
我懇請大家
...for their patience and understanding."
給予我耐心和理解
You're an asshole, Hancock!
你是個混蛋，漢考克！
Asshole!
混蛋！
"Life here can be difficult for me.
其實我的生活也不輕松
After all, I'm the only one of my kind.
畢竟超人只有我一個
During my incarceration, I will be participating...
監禁期間我會主動配合
...in alcohol- and anger-management treatment."
去戒酒和參加情緒控制治療
You're a drunk bum!
你就是個醉鬼！
"You deserve better from me. I can be better. I will be better."
我本可以做得更好 我能做得更好，也會去努力
All right.
好了
CALIFORNIA DEPARTMENT OF CORRECTIONS
（加利福尼亞管教部）
Good morning, ladies. Welcome to your new home...
小姐們早上好，歡迎來到你們的新家
It is the duty of each of you to remember your inmate serial number.
你們有義務記住室友的編號
Turn to your right.
向右轉
Turn to your left.
向左轉
Okay, scumbags. Let's go.
混混們，快走
Give me the hand, playboy.
伸出手來，小子
CALIFORNIA STATE PRISON JOHN HANCOCK
加州監獄，約翰•漢考克
I see you, punk!
等著瞧吧，笨蛋
Oh, I get it.
我明白了
I put some... Most of you in here.
你們有些人…其實大部分是我弄進來的
Yes, you did.
說得沒錯
I can understand you feeling some kind of way about that.
我理解你們气儿不順
What?
什么？
So I'm gonna do me and I'm gonna let you do you.
咱們井水不犯河水
I don't want no trouble.
我不想惹麻煩
All right?
這樣行嗎？
I just wanna go to my cell.
我現在只想回我牢房
- That ain't gonna happen. - Nope.
- 想得美 - 是啊
Excuse me.
讓一下
Excuse me, please.
請你們讓一下
Deadly.
你死定了
If you don't move, your head is going up his ass.
不讓開的話，我把你腦袋塞進他屁股里
Y'all fellas sure you wanna ride this train?
你倆想跟我叫板？
Choo, choo, asshole.
來啊，混蛋
Get him out! Get him out!
把他弄出來！把他弄出來！
Did you shove a man's head up another man's ass?
你真把一個人的腦袋塞到另一個人的屁股里了？
We're gonna... We're gonna circle back to that.
這個…這個回頭再討論
The DA's office wants your sentence to run eight years.
地方檢察官想要判你8年監禁
It's a big number, but not something we didn't anticipate.
判刑挺重，不過也不算太出格
You know, our plan is... What are you doing?
咱們的計划是…你在干嘛？
It sounded like you said they want me to spend eight years in this shithole.
你剛才說我要在這鬼地方呆上8年
Eight is more like four and a half with good behavior.
表現良好四年半就能出來
But it's irrelevant because with you out of the picture...
刑期多少不是重點，因為你不在了的話
...and with the crime rate going up through the roof...
到時犯罪率就會飛漲
...the DA and the cops, they're all gonna call for your immediate release.
檢察官和警察會立刻放了你
They're gonna demand it. Where are you going? Sit down.
他們會需要你的，你在干嘛？坐下來
Hey. Hey. Stop right there.
呆著別走
- Stop it. Hancock. - Move.
- 停下來，漢考克 - 讓開
- Hancock! - Get back!
- 漢考克！ - 快回來！
You're being a coward!
你就是個膽小鬼
- Who you talking to? - I'm talking to you.
- 說誰呢？ - 我說你呢
- Who are you talking to, Ray? - Stop pretending that you do not care.
- 再說一遍？ - 別裝著你不在乎
You have a calling. You're a hero, Hancock.
英雄有英雄的命，漢考克
You're gonna be miserable the rest of your life until you accept that.
要是不面對現實，你會痛苦一輩子
Trust me. Trust this plan, this process. Just stay in here.
相信我，相信這計划，留下來
When they call, a hero's what we're gonna give them.
等他們需要你時，你就會是真正的英雄了
How we gonna do that, Ray?
咱們怎么做？
All right, guys, let's start sharing.
大伙說說自己的進展吧
- Don? You had something? - Yeah.
- 唐，你要說嗎？ - 我有話說
Yeah, I think I might've had a little bit of a breakthrough.
我覺得可能有點突破性進展
Good for you.
不錯嘛
Yeah, I mean, I realized that breaking necks is... It's easy.
我原以為扭斷脖子很容易
But I'm sitting there and I'm staring at myself in the mirror...
可我坐著看到鏡子里的自己
...and I thought, "This is tough." - Yeah, it sounds tough.
- 我想了想，其實還是挺難的 - 是啊，听著就恐怖
Why do you always laugh?
你干嘛老是笑我？
Picturing you looking at the mirror. It would scare the shit out of me.
想想你照鏡子的樣子我就嚇得尿褲子了
Every time I'm talking, he completely ruins the cycle.
每次輪到我講話，他都亂插嘴
Now, let's watch the crosstalk.
那就先讓他說好了
I'm not gonna share anymore if he keeps doing that.
他要老是這樣，我以后可不說了
No, no, no.
別這樣啊
- Keep sharing. - Let's move on.
- 繼續吧 - 咱們繼續
Mr. Hancock, do you wanna share today?
漢考克先生，今天想跟大家說點什么？
Pass.
沒有
Your landing is your first impression. It's your superhero handshake.
著陸是你給人的第一印象 就好比握手一樣
Don't come in too hot, okay? Don't come in too boozy.
別降落得太猛了，也別喝酒
And don't land on a $ 100,000 Mercedes. All right?
別踩到十万塊錢的梅賽德斯車上
People have to be happy that you've arrived.
你的到來應該讓大家愉快
Mr. Hancock, your share.
漢考克先生，有什么說的嗎？
Pass.
沒有
So you've used the door and the building's still intact.
你進門后，房子也還完好無損
People are happy that you've arrived. They feel safe.
大家就很高興你來了，因為他們有安全感
There's an officer and he's done a good job...
要是有個警官干得不錯
...so tell him he's done a good job.
你就告訴他干得挺好
What the hell did I have to come for if he's done a good job?
他要做得好還要我干嘛？
Oh, man!
我的天！
KBLA radio, AM 850.
這是KBLA電台，調頻850千赫
Today's big story, no surprise here: Hancock. What's your take?
今天的話題毫不奇怪 還是你對漢考克怎么看
I, for one, have had enough of this guy.
就拿我來說吧，我是受夠了
I'm glad he's doing time around bars and I hope they don't let him off easy.
很高興他進監獄了，可別輕易放了他
Let my cousin Pookie out.
不如放了我表兄帕齊吧
"I see you don't wear a bulletproof vest, security officer.
你說過：“警官，看來你沒穿防彈衣”
I respect your courage...
“我佩服你的膽量…”
...because bullets don't bounce off you, they bounce off me."
“因為你不像我一樣刀槍不入”
This city is being run by gangs and drug dealers.
黑幫和毒販控制了這地方
Hancock makes them shake in their boots.
漢考克能讓他們膽戰心惊
He doesn't tie a pretty ribbon around it, but he gets the job done.
雖說不是干得很漂亮，但他能完成任務
Besides, he's hot.
而且他還很性感
Let me hear you say it. Let me hear you say, "Good job."
你得說出來，跟我說，“干得不錯”
G...
干…
Goo...
干得…
Mr. Hancock, would you like to share?
漢考克先生，有什么要說的嗎？
- Pass. - Good.
- 沒有 - 干得…
Good.
干得…
Good j...
干得不…
Good job.
干得不…錯
Jail watch, day five, and true to his word, Hancock remains incarcerated.
監獄觀察，第5天，漢考克仍信守諾言
Meanwhile, crime is still on the rise.
与此同時，犯罪率仍在上升
The L.A.P.D. Is reporting increases of up to 30 percent...
根据市警察局的報告，過去的5天里
...in the last five days that Hancock has been behind bars.
竟上升了30%，而漢考克仍在服刑
- Hancock! Hey, Hancock! - Hey, little buddy.
- 漢考克！漢考克！ - 嘿，小老弟
- Hancock. We brought you something! - Hey, hey.
- 漢考克，我們給你拿好東西來了 - 嘿，嘿
Hey, what's up, Hancock?
你還好嗎，漢考克？
Where's...? Where's Ray?
瑞怎么沒來？
No, it's just us. Ray's working.
就我們倆，瑞在上班
Aaron really wanted to come and see you...
艾倫很想過來看你
...so we just dropped by with some Spaghetti Madness.
給你拿來了超級意大利面
I should probably let the guard check for keys...
可能得先讓警衛看一下有沒有鑰匙
- No, no. Here. - Okay. Here you go.
- 不用了 - 好吧，給你
Oh, you brought me meatballs, huh?
給我帶來了肉丸子？
- Just dig in. - Oh, man, look at that. Look at that.
- 開吃吧！ - 快瞧瞧
- That's a good meatball. - Thanks, Hancock.
- 丸子很不錯 - 謝謝，漢考克
Ray is a good man.
瑞很善良
Whatever this is you're doing, don't let him down.
不管你現在在做什么，不要辜負了他
Okay?
好嗎？
Okay. Well, we should probably go, buddy.
好了，咱們該走了，小伙子
- Already? I wanna stay with Hancock. - Yeah. Sweetheart...
- 這就走？我想陪陪漢考克 - 是啊，甜心…
...we have to go. Come on, say goodbye to Hancock.
咱們得走了，來跟他說再見吧
Here, Hancock. It's my favorite one, and I want you to have it.
把它留給你吧，我最喜歡的，給你了
- That was very sweet. - Thanks, Mom.
- 你真好 - 謝謝媽媽
Come here.
過來
Mr. Hancock, would you like to share?
漢考克先生，有什么想說的嗎？
Pass.
沒有
All right. Phillip?
好了，該菲利普了？
I love you guys, man.
我愛你們！
- We love you. - We love you too, Phillip.
- 我們也是 - 我們也是，菲利普
For when they call.
為你出山准備的
- I ain't wearing that, Ray. - Yes, you are.
- 我可不想穿那個 - 你想穿的
- Oh, no, I'm not. - No, you are.
- 我不想穿
Actually, I'm not, Ray.
我是真不想穿
You think you're not, but you are.
你就別欺騙你自己了
I will fight crime butt-ass naked before I fight it in that, Ray.
我宁可光著屁股打架也不穿
You know, you have fought naked. We've got that. That's on YouTube.
你已經光屁股打斗過了，Youtube上有
Hancock, this is a uniform. A uniform represents purpose.
漢考克，這是制服，代表著使命
Doctors, policemen, firemen, right?
就像醫生、警察和消防員一樣
- It represents a calling. - It's been two weeks.
- 這代表著你的天職 - 已經兩個星期了
- Yeah? - Nobody out there is missing me, Ray.
- 是嗎？ - 沒人想著我
Just be patient. You gotta trust me on this. All right?
耐心點，你要相信我的判斷，好嗎？
Perimeter breach, perimeter breach.
衝破禁區，衝破禁區
Asshole!
混蛋！
You're still a fake-ass punk.
你依舊是個混蛋騙子啊
Damn!
見鬼！
Mr. Hancock?
漢考克先生？
It's your share.
輪到你了
Pass.
我沒有什么好說的
- Come on, man, try it. Let it out. - Come on, John.
- 來吧，伙計，試試啊，說出來 - 說說啊
I don't have nothing.
我真沒啥好說的
There's nothing on your mind? Come on, John.
不可能什么都沒有，試試看
- It's cool, man. - Come on.
- 沒關系的 - 來吧
- Do it.
- 說說看
First time for everything.
凡事開頭難
- Feels good to release, now. - Let it heal. Come on, man, try it.
- 放下顧慮就好了 - 管用的，試試看
Come in here all these days, you don't have anything to share?
進來這么多天了，沒有什么要說的嗎？
I'm Hancock, and I drink and stuff.
我叫漢考克，我有酗酒的毛病
All right. Thanks for sharing.
不錯，謝謝你分享
- Okay. - Thank you.
- 好的 - 謝謝
- All right. - That's awesome.
- 挺不錯的
- That's a clap. Yeah. - There you go. Good share.
- 值得鼓掌 - 說得不錯
Hey, Hancock.
漢考克
Come on, get up.
快起來
- You got a phone call. - Take a message.
- 有你電話 - 讓他留言
It's the chief of police.
警察局長的電話
He says he needs your help.
他說需要你幫忙
SWAT
（洛杉磯特种部隊）
The trapped officer's husband is Corporal Joseph Blake...
被困警官的丈夫是布雷克下士
...who was killed last year in Iraq...
去年犧牲在伊拉克
...leaving her two small children. We are waiting for the latest news...
留下了她和兩個孩子，我們還在等新消息
...but apparently there are three suspects and...
看起來有3名嫌疑犯
What's going on?
怎么回事？
I'm out!
沒子彈了
Stay down! Stay down!
趴下！趴下！
Stay down!
趴下！
- Get out! - Get down!
- 快出來！ - 趴下
Get it down!
趴下
IPE BANK & TRUST
（公企信托銀行）
Let's go! Everybody's gotta get back! Let's go!
所有人退后！快點行動！
Back! Move!
后退！快點
We got perimeters set up on the north, east and south sides.
北邊、東邊、南邊都拉上了警戒線
The west side is open.
西面還留著口
Don't break the building, don't break the building.
別撞坏大樓，別撞坏大樓
What?
干嘛？
It's a little tight. What you got?
衣服有點緊，什么情況？
Bank job. I got at least eight hostages. Four bad guys.
銀行搶劫，至少8名人質，4名罪犯
Officer pinned down. We can't get to her.
一名警官受困，靠近不了她
They been spraying the hell out of us all morning. And...
整個上午他們一直對著我們掃射
They got some kind of heavy artillery. Fifty caliber or bigger.
他們還有种重型炮，50口徑，或者更大
- I don't know if that matters to you. - No, I'm good.
- 不知道你行不行 - 我會沒事儿的
Good job.
干得不錯
Really, good job.
干得真不錯
Get down!
快趴下
It's Hancock!
是漢考克！
Take him out!
打死他！
Good job!
干得不錯
Do I have permission to touch your body?
我能碰您的身体嗎？
Yes!
可以！
It's not sexual.
我沒那個意思
Not that you're not an attractive woman.
我不是說你不迷人
- You're a very attractive woman... - Get me the f% % &#k out of here!
- 你實際上很迷人 - 把我帶走就行了！
He's on the move!
他開始移動了
Good job.
干得不錯
- Are you hit anywhere? - My leg!
- 哪中彈了？ - 大腿
- Hancock! - Good job.
- 漢考克！ - 干得不錯
You said that. I need you to end this now.
你說過了，現在擺平這事儿吧
Check the flanks.
檢查側面
Secure the perimeter.
看好四周
Spread out!
散開！
They're gonna come around the back.
他們肯定在后面襲擊
What happened to him?
他怎么了？
Where'd he go? Where'd he go?
他哪去了？他哪去了？
What is happening?
怎么回事儿？
- I heard you was in the slammer. - Out early.
- 我听說你在監獄里 - 提前釋放了
- Why's that? - Good behavior.
- 怎么可能？ - 表現良好
Do you know what this is?
知道這是什么嗎？
I'm guessing it's some kind of detonator-type deal.
我猜又是炸藥威脅那一套
There's 8 pounds of C-4 strapped to each and every one of them.
他們每人身上都綁著7斤C4炸藥
This is a spring-loaded dead man's switch.
這是彈簧触發開關
If my thumb comes off it:
我拇指一松開
BOOM!
轟！
And now, since we've had a little change of plan...
現在既然情況有點變化
...between the police showing up...
惊動了警察
...and you sucking out all of my associates...
你還把我伙計們都吸走了
...I want you to break into the vault.
所以你得幫我去保險庫
You'll find three quarter-ton pallets of small bills inside.
托盤上有0.75吨的小額鈔票
Thirty million dollars.
3千万美元
And you're gonna carry it for me.
你給我拿過來
You are gonna get me safely away from here with the money...
你還得護送我帶著錢安全离開
...or else they'll be cleaning up these hostages with a mop.
要不他們就得用拖把清理人質肉灰了
I'm gonna have to say no to that.
我不得不拒絕你的要求
I'm really trying to turn over a new leaf.
我正努力改過自新
I will blow up this entire building, you asshole.
我會把整棟樓炸飛的，你個混蛋
I really don't like that word.
這詞儿我真不太喜歡
I will blow them sky-high...
我會把他們炸上天
...and their blood will be on your hands.
讓你手上濺上鮮血
Do you hear me, asshole?
听懂了嗎，混蛋？
Call me a asshole...
你有本事…
...one more time.
再說一遍
Ass...
混…
- Go, go, go. Move in! - Go on, you're safe!
- 走，走，走！衝進去 - 快走，你沒事了
- Let's go. Let's go. - Take it right in. Let's go.
- 大家行動 - 帶它衝進去，行動
Bring it around now.
馬上帶過來
Keep your hand on that trigger.
手按住開關
- Good job. - No. You, good job.
- 干得不錯 - 其實是你干得不錯！
- Thank you. - Good job.
- 謝謝 - 干得不錯
Hancock!
漢考克！
Say hi to your fans. Look what you got.
和粉絲打聲招呼，你應得的
Here we go. This way.
咱們這邊走
- Hancock. At the bank today, intense. - Thank you.
- 漢考克，今天銀行那儿真激烈啊 - 謝謝你
Smile.
笑一個
Good job, Hancock!
干得不錯，漢考克！
Hey. Boy, they'll let anybody in here, huh?
老天，大家都來了
Hancock, meet these guys. This is Mike Kilbourne and Jeremy Himmel.
漢考克，這是麥克和杰里米
Gigantic fans. Insane!
我們可是你的超級粉絲
These guys are partners at the biggest ad firm.
頂級廣告公司的兩個大股東
You never call, man.
你怎么不給我們打電話
- I have called. A couple of times. - Water under the bridge, man.
- 我打過，有几次 - 以前的事儿就過去吧
Could you guys get used to this or what?
你倆倒挺鎮靜的
How'd you two meet?
你們怎么認識的？
I was married once before.
我以前結過一次婚
First wife...
第一任妻子
...she died giving birth to Aaron.
生艾倫的時候難產過世了
It's another dinner. But... But...
這個改天再說，反正后來吧…
So there I am, I'm with this beautiful little baby.
我就帶著可愛儿子
I don't know what the hell to do.
每天還是無所适從
And I was in the supermarket...
有天在超市里面
...and I'm in the baby aisle...
我正在嬰儿用品區
...and I've got a brand of diapers in each hand.
兩手拿著一個牌子的尿布
I'm staring at them, but I don't know how I'm gonna get through the day.
我看傻眼了，不知道怎么熬過那一天
An angel...
一個天使…
...sees me.
發現了我
She knew. She was... She gave me this look.
她好像一眼就看透了我
And even in the trance I was in, I knew that somebody somewhere...
雖然我還深陷困境，可我明白
...was throwing me a little rope.
有人已經向我伸出了援助的手
You know?
你知道的
Starting that day, you really put my life back together. Right?
那天起，你真的讓我生活恢复原樣了
- You're drunk. - So? Come here.
- 你喝多了 - 是嗎？來吧
What about you, buddy?
你呢，兄弟？
You're from another planet, aren't you?
你該不會是外星人吧？
No, man, I'm from Miami.
不是，我是邁阿密人
You didn't come in on, like, a meteor or...?
你沒踩著流星什么的過來？
Nope. Woke up in a hospital, first thing I remember.
沒，只記得是在醫院醒過來
Government hospital, yes? Experimenting on you and...
公立醫院吧？正對你做實驗呢…
No, Ray. Regular old Miami emergency room.
不是，就邁阿密那种老急診室
- Come on. - My skull was fractured.
- 得啦！ - 我頭骨裂了
They told me I tried to stop a mugging.
他們說我本想阻止搶劫
- Somebody knocked you out. - I guess I was a regular guy before...
- 有人給你打昏了 - 我想我以前就是普通人
...and when I woke up, I was changed.
醒來以后我就變了
The hospital nurse tried to put a needle in my arm...
醫院護士想要在我胳膊上扎針
...and it just broke against my skin.
連皮都碰不破
And then my skull healed in, like, an hour.
一個小時左右，我頭骨就自動愈合
The doctors were astounded...
醫生們大吃一惊
...and they wanted to know my story.
想要听我講我的身世
Just like you. But I couldn't tell them. I don't know who I am.
就跟你們一樣好奇，可我不知道，全忘了
Amnesia.
健忘症
- You know, the blow to the head. - Yeah, well, that's what they figured.
- 因為腦袋挨的一下？ - 是啊，他們也是這么說
- You don't remember anything? - No.
- 什么都不記得了？ - 是的
Only thing I had in my pocket was...
我口袋里剩下的東西
...bubble gum...
只有口香糖
...two movie tickets.
和兩張電影票
Boris Karloff, Frankenstein.
伯里斯演的電影《科學怪人》
But no ID, nothing.
我沒身份証，什么都沒有
I went to sign out, the nurse asked me for my John Hancock.
出院時，護士叫我寫上約翰•漢考克
I actually thought that's who I was.
我還以為我就叫這名
How come I didn't hear any of this, didn't read about it in any newspapers?
我怎么從沒听說，或是在報上看到這事儿？
It was probably in the papers 80 years ago.
80年前的報紙肯定登過
Eighty years ago?
80年前？
Oh, I don't age. This is it.
我不會衰老的，就是這樣
- That's nice. - Gotta wonder, though:
- 那很好啊 - 可我禁不住地想
What kind of bastard must I have been...
我究竟混蛋到什么地步…
...that nobody was there to claim me?
才讓家人都不來認我？
I mean, I'm not the most charming guy in the world...
雖然不像大家所說
...so I've been told, but...
我是世界第一帥哥，可是…
...nobody?
…沒人找我？
Whoever it was they'd be dead by now, anyway.
不管怎樣，就算有人現在也死了
Hey, Mary. You all right, baby?
瑪麗，你沒事吧，寶貝儿？
Yeah. Too much wine.
沒事，酒喝太多了
I am a lightweight.
我酒量太小
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
You ain't do nothing.
你又沒做錯什么
This was a nice dinner, Ray.
晚宴不錯
- It was a good one. - Almost call this fun.
- 相當不錯 - 能說得上很愉快
That didn't tire you out, coming up the stairs?
你就不累嗎？上樓來
- Not really. - I'm real spinny.
- 我沒事 - 我覺得天旋地轉
Could've just flown me upstairs.
我都能轉上樓梯去了
- I could've done without that. - Get your shoes off here.
- 沒你扶我也能轉上去 - 把鞋脫了吧
All right, that's all you're getting off of me though.
就准脫這件，別的不行
You believe in me, don't you, Hancock?
你相信我吧，漢考克？
- Of course, Ray. I believe in you. - Help me up here.
- 我當然相信你 - 拉我一把
I got something to say to you.
我有話對你說
Listen to me. This is important.
听我說，這很重要
You are like a Dodger Dog.
你就像狗不理包子
It's something people don't think they're gonna like...
開始大家以為不會喜歡
...then they try it and they love it, right? It hits the spot.
吃一口就愛上了，特對他們口味
It's good for the soul. You're like the world's Dodger Dog.
還有益身心，而你就是世界的狗不理包子
I don't know. But you know what I mean, right?
可能我沒說明白，領會精神吧
You're gonna do great.
你肯定能成大事
You're gonna fix everything.
你會把一切都理順的
- You get some sleep, Ray. - You sleep tight too.
- 你早點睡吧 - 你也睡個好覺
Hancock tucking me in.
漢考克幫我蓋過被子啊
All right, he's asleep.
好了，他睡著了
- Okay, thanks. Good night. - Good night.
- 好的，謝謝了，晚安 - 晚安
Look, I just don't want you to think that... That Ray...
我想說瑞喝成那樣不是因為…
...you know, drinks like that, because...
我桌上的舉止…
- Oh, no. - This was just kind of...
- 不會的 - 其實他很高興
...a celebratory night. - No, I understand.
- …今晚本該慶祝 - 我理解
- Yeah, I know that. - Okay.
- 明白 - 那就好
The damn babysitter never cleans up after herself.
可惡的保姆吃完了總是不收拾干淨
You have a bruise on your hand.
你手擦傷了
Yeah, I don't... I don't know what that is.
是啊，我也不知道怎么弄的
I've been feeling kind of funny.
我近來感覺有點奇怪
You...
你…
You should go.
你得走了
Getting late.
天太晚了
If Ray finds out about me...
我丈夫要是知道了
...you're dead.
你就死定了
Joan, we're gonna take care of that, okay? Don't you worry.
約翰，我們會收拾好的，別擔心
Hi, honey.
嗨，親愛的
Breakfast?
早飯？
Hancock sneezed, huh?
漢考克打了噴嚏
Can you believe it? It's amazing that you slept through that.
你相信嗎？啊嚏！真奇怪你沒醒過來
- You're a good sleeper. - Holy shit.
- 你睡得真香啊 - 天哪
I'm not gonna say I told you so, but...
不能說是我告訴你的啊
You told me he was gonna sneeze a hole through the house?
他一個噴嚏都能打個洞？
I just said him being around...
我早說過他在的話…
Oh, sweetheart, can you get that? Thanks.
親愛的幫我弄開好嗎？謝謝
- Oh, God, you strong man. - I got it.
- 你力气真大 - 搞定了
But you don't worry about anything.
你什么都不用擔心
I already apologized to the neighbors. Called State Farm.
我跟鄰居道了歉，也告訴了保險公司
Everything is taken care of.
都解決好了
You just...
你就…
...enjoy that breakfast.
…安心吃飯吧
What's this? Are we going on vacation? Are we?
這是什么？咱們要去度假？
Just the three of us.
就咱們三口
- End of the summer? - Tonight.
- 夏天過后？ - 今晚就走
- Tonight? - Spur of the moment.
- 今晚？ - 我是靈机一動
- Tonight might be a little tough. - Come on. The three of us?
- 今晚就走有點難 - 來嘛！三口旅行？
Me in a bikini?
我穿比基尼泳裝
- Sounds good. - Let's go somewhere.
- 听著不錯 - 隨便去哪儿
Knock, knock.
敲門啦
Gesundheit.
老天保佑你
I was just telling Ray here, I hope you're done sneezing...
我正跟他說呢，希望你把噴嚏都打完了
...because I don't think our house could take much more...
要是你再打噴嚏的話
...of your sneezing.
房子可受不了
Yeah, sometimes I sneeze when there's dust...
是啊，有時候灰塵太多
...or if I get really surprised.
或者我大吃一惊的時候就打
That's unfortunate. This is Kilbourne.
你真是不幸，克伯恩來電話了
Mike? How you doing?
麥克？你怎么樣？
It was great to see you too.
能見到你我也很高興
Yep. Well...
嗯，那個…
Right. Go ahead, shoot.
是啊，繼續，有啥說啥
Okay. I got a pen right here.
等會，我拿支筆
Right. No, I know.
嗯，我明白
It's right here in my hand.
拿到了
I am warning you.
我警告你
All right, go ahead.
好的，繼續
Okay, good.
好的
Now... And that's still in 310, right?
那就3點10分見？
Hang on one second.
稍等一下
Do me a favor?
安靜點好嗎？
I'm sorry, Mike. Yeah.
對不起，麥克
We're gonna talk.
我們得談談
Go away.
給我走開
Well, it is something that I'm really excited about.
對這事儿我是挺興奮的
- I'm gonna do this all day. - Shut... Shut up.
- 我陪你玩一天都行 - 小點聲！
I... I suppose...
我想…
- Fine. We'll talk, okay? - We will.
- 談就談，行了吧？ - 确實得說說
And when we're done talking, you go away and you leave my family alone.
扯清楚了，你就消失，离我家人遠點
- My place at 4:00. - Whatever.
- 我家4點見面吧 - 隨你便
It means... Well, I'd rather not talk numbers now.
電話里談錢不太好吧
I'd like to save them for the pitch. So let's just set a time.
別這么早就定調，咱們還是安排個時間
That's good with me. I will see you then. All right.
我沒問題，那回頭見，好的
Yeah, 3:30. Great.
好的，3點半，好的
Hon, is it hot in here?
老婆，屋里怎么這么熱
He hurt you, didn't he?
他傷害你們了，是吧？
Come on, use your words.
來啊，說出來
How did it make you feel?
你們有什么感覺？
Sore.
疼啊
Bad.
糟透了
It's because he took your power. And you have to get your power back.
因為他把你們的力量都奪走了 你們得再奪回來
And no one will give you your power back. You have to go out and take it.
除了自己去爭取，沒人會還給你們
You understand me?
明白嗎？
We're gonna go find Hancock...
我們去把漢考克揪出來
...and get your power back.
奪回你們的力量
Well, I'm here.
我人來了
Yup.
是啊
- You wanna do it? - Do what?
- 你到底想不想做？ - 做什么？
I don't have time for this, okay? You ask the questions...
我沒時間跟你鬧，你先問問題…
...I answer them honestly and then you leave L.A.
我實話實說，然后你离開洛杉磯
I ain't leaving L.A.
我才不离開洛杉磯呢
All right, all right. Jeez.
行了，行了，天哪
Don't.
省省吧
Ask.
問吧
- You and I. - "You and l" what?
- 我和你 - 什么我和你
- We're the same. - No.
- 咱們是一類人 - 不是
I'm stronger.
我更強大
Really?
真的？
Oh, yeah.
是啊
Who are we?
我們是誰？
Gods, angels. Different cultures call us by different names.
神靈、天使，不同時代有不同的稱呼
Now all of a sudden, it's "superhero."
現在突然編出個“超級英雄”的詞儿來
- Are there more of us? - There were.
- 還有其他人嗎？ - 曾經有過
They all died.
他們都死了
It's just the two of us.
現在就剩咱們倆了
What is this?
現在是怎么回事？
Who are we to each other?
咱們什么關系？
- We're brother and sister. - That's a lie.
- 我們是兄妹關系 - 撒謊吧
- No, I'm your sister. - That is a lie.
- 我是你妹妹 - 你騙人
- I'm your sister.
- 騙人
Sisters don't kiss brothers the way you kissed me last night.
是妹妹就不會像昨天那樣親我
You're lying, deal's off.
你撒謊吧，合同取消
Let's go see how Ray feels about this.
我看你丈夫怎么說
Get your ass back here!
你滾回來！
I'm telling!
我就去說！
The AllHeart symbol will be known globally...
“全心全意”標志…
...as a symbol...
將會在全球聞名
...that represents companies that are committed to changing the world.
代表著那些愿意拯救世界的公司
They can give away their sustenance goods, okay?
他們會免費提供生活必需品
Food, drugs, power, clothing, for free.
食品、藥品、能源、衣服，全免費
- We were talking about Hancock... - Number two.
- 我們想聊聊漢考克 - 第二點…
You stay away from me and my family.
你离我和我家人遠點
You are not gonna do this to me again.
你不能再對我這樣了
What? I don't know what you're talking about.
什么？你什么意思？
- Hey! - I love you, Hancock!
- 嘿！ - 我愛你，漢考克！
It can't work. It always ends the same way.
咱們碰頭沒好處，最后總是不歡而散
Persia. Greece. Brooklyn.
不管是在波斯、希腊，還是在布魯克林
Brooklyn? I've never been to Brooklyn.
布魯克林？我從沒去過那儿
I have put up with your bullshit for 3000 years...
我都忍了你三千年了
...and I am done! Done, you listening?
我受夠了，夠了！听到了嗎！
- I don't know what you're talking about! - Finally, I am happy!
- 你說的我全不明白 - 現在我總算有個幸福家庭
- You are not gonna mess with that! - I don't know what you're talking about!
- 你又來添亂！ - 我不知道你在胡扯什么
I hate to burst your little crazy-lady bubble...
害你這女瘋子失望了
...but it must not have been all that great because I don't remember you.
我看是你單相思，要不我肯定記得
Call me crazy...
叫我瘋子？
...one more time.
再說一遍
Cuckoo.
小瘋瘋
All right, hold it. All right.
好啊，先等等
You better not hit me with that truck.
警告你別用卡車砸我
For companies to qualify, they need to prove they are a leader in the global...
想要取得資格，企業要証明是世界頂尖…
We wanna talk about Mr. Hancock.
我們想聊聊漢考克先生
They're committed to bettering the world.
他們要致力于改善這個世界
They can do this in four ways. This is how they...
可以有以下4种方式…
The most important thing with AllHeart is brand recognition.
最重要的是打響品牌
I've mocked up these examples here...
我又設計了些樣本
...in Tokyo, London, Dubai, Paris.
估計在東京、倫敦、迪拜和巴黎就這樣
Oh, no.
噢，糟糕
We need maximum exposure, market penetra...
我們要大力宣傳，打入市場…
Is it snowing?
下雪了？
Stop. Stop it.
停下，別這樣
Stop. Stop. Stop! All right, let's just...
停下！好了，咱們就…
Get off me!
放開我！
Stop. Stop!
停下！
Get off!
放開！
- Get off me! - Listen to me!
- 放開我！ - 听我說！
- I hate you! - I am sorry!
- 我恨你！ - 對不起！
Whoever I am, whatever I did... Look at me.
不管我是誰，干過什么，看著我
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
I don't remember.
我不記得了
You are the most beautiful thing I have ever seen.
你是我見過的最美的女人
Oh, my God.
噢，糟了
Why were you flying? You were flying, Mary.
你怎么會飛？瑪麗，你剛才在飛啊
- Yeah, she was definitely flying, Ray. - Okay, I was flying.
- 她剛在确實在飛 - 好了，我是在飛
And I'm very strong as well.
而且我也有超能力
- It's just the way we are. - "We"?
- 我們是超人 - “我們”？
Me and him, it's just us now. The others paired up and died.
就剩我和他兩個人了 其他人配對結合后都死了
You didn't say anything about pairing up at the trailer.
剛才在拖車那儿你沒說配對的事
- You were at his trailer. - This is hard to explain.
- 你去過他的拖車？ - 很難解釋清楚
- Great, I'm all ears. - Me too.
- 那好，我洗耳恭听 - 我也是
Do me a favor, just give me and my wife one moment.
拜托你能不能讓我和妻子單獨呆會？
- Don't bring it here, Ray. - The adults are talking.
- 別針對我啊 - 大人說話別插嘴
Technically speaking...
嚴格說來…
...he's my husband.
他才是我丈夫
Holy shit.
真見鬼了
- What? - We broke up decades ago.
- 什么？ - 我們几十年前分的手
Long before you were born. He just can't remember.
你出生之前老早的事儿了，他又忘了
But you can, right? You knew?
可你記得，不是嗎？
That's something you bring up on a first date, Mary.
這种事約會第一天就該提出來
"I don't like to travel. I'm allergic to cats. I'm immortal."
“我不愛旅游，對貓過敏，還長生不老”
Those are some things you give a heads-up on.
這种事你得事先提個醒
Whatever we are, we were built in twos, okay?
不管怎樣，我倆天生一對的，懂嗎？
We're drawn to each other.
我們注定互相吸引
No matter how far I run, he's always there.
不管我跑多遠，他也能追過來
He finds me. It's physics.
他總能找到我，就像磁鐵
Are you saying that you two are fated to be together?
你說你倆命中注定到一起？
I've lived for a very long time, Ray.
我活了這么長時間
And the one thing I learned...
明白一個道理
...fate doesn't decide everything.
決定一切的不是命運
People get to choose.
我們能做出自己的選擇
And you chose...
所以你就選擇…
...to let me think I was here alone.
讓我還以為自己孤單一人？
I didn't think you'd miss what you didn't remember.
我沒想到你想尋找你的過去
Great. Now what?
好极了，現在還怎么著？
I didn't plan for this.
我也沒想這樣
Prison authorities confirmed...
監獄管理層确認…
...that the prisoner uprising was led by Kenneth "Red" Parker, Jr...
正是帕克挑起了監獄暴動
...who was also the leader of last week's Spring Street bank robbery.
他也是上星期銀行搶劫案的主犯
At least eight prisoners are not accounted for.
現在至少8人下落不明
More information on the prison riot in Norwalk.
接下來是更多有關諾瓦克監獄暴動的消息
Construction workers at the prison were knocked unconscious.
監獄里的建筑工人被人打昏
The prisoners stole the workers' clothes...
囚犯換上了工人衣服
...and it's feared at least some of them have escaped.
怀疑他們當中有些已經逃走
Parker is considered a criminal mastermind.
帕克作案詭計多端
He is very effective at using psychological persuasion...
他很擅長玩心理戰術
...to organize criminals from different backgrounds.
拉攏不同作案背景的犯罪分子
He is a former psychology professor from Stanford University.
他曾經是斯坦福大學的心理學教授
While there, he organized a notorious criminal network...
就在那里組織過臭名昭著的犯罪集團
...comprised of graduate students from diverse...
包括了各种背景的研究生…
Ninety-one ten.
91塊1毛
Ninety-one ten? You gotta be shitting me.
91塊1？你開玩笑吧
Ninety-one ten.
91.1元
Highway robbery.
大白天明搶啊
- 911
911報警電話
- What? - I'm taking the money.
- 你想怎么樣？ - 我要拿錢走
I can relate to that.
我可以高興地答應你
You know? If you want something...
不過前提是，你想要什么東西
...nobody can stop you from taking it...
沒人攔得住
...you just take it, right?
你就能拿走了，對吧？
I like that.
勇气可嘉
But can you take it?
可你拿得走嗎？
My Zagnut bar versus your gun.
我用巧克力糖對你手槍
Sorry about your window.
抱歉弄坏了窗戶
- I need Room 1020. - Clear!
- 准備好急診室1020 - 讓開
I need Room 1020.
准備好急診室1020
I need IV line, blood quality, CBC, electrolytes, a PT, and...
要輸液管、血液化驗、電解液和理療
Where's his IV line?
輸液管在哪？
- That's not gonna work. - I'm in.
- 針扎不進去的 - 扎進去了
What's happening?
怎么回事？
This just in. John Hancock has been rushed...
最新消息，漢考克已經緊急送到…
...to Los Angeles General Hospital.
洛杉磯綜合醫院搶救
Hancock is in serious condition with multiple gunshot wounds.
他身中數槍，有生命危險
No story yet as to how this happened to him...
我們還不知道事情經過
...but we will continue to cover this story live. Reporting live from L. A...
不過我們會繼續現場追蹤報道
MERCY GENERAL HOSPITAL
（濟慈綜合醫院）
- Any lead on the assailant? - Mr. Embrey!
- 有襲擊者的線索了嗎？ - 安伯雷先生！
Just a couple of questions, sir, please.
就問您兩個問題
Can you describe how it happened?
您能說說是怎么回事嗎？
From what I've heard, he was trying to stop a robbery.
我听說他想要阻止一次搶劫
Do you know if special ammunition was used in the gun that shot him?
是不是手槍用了什么特殊子彈？
Not that I'm aware of.
這我沒听說
Could this have to do with the mysterious woman?
与神秘女超人有關系嗎？
- He was seen battling her. - I do not have that answer.
- 有人目擊他們打斗過 - 這事我無可奉告
Could this woman be more powerful than Hancock?
是不是她比漢考克能力更強？
Here are the lab results for 209.
這是209床的化驗結果
You're becoming mortal.
你正變成凡人
It's us...
要是咱們接近了
...being close to each other.
就會變成這樣
It's never happened this fast before.
可從來沒這么快過
You have to leave.
你得离開我
The further you get from me, the better you're gonna feel.
离我越遠，你感覺就會越好
You'll start getting your powers back...
你的能力也會回來
...and be flying and breaking things...
你還能飛來飛去，四處搞搞破坏
...and saving people before you know it.
一不留神就可能救了誰的命
Well, it's like I said, we were built in pairs.
我告訴過你，咱們是配對而生的
And when we get close to our opposites, we lose our power.
互相接近以后，咱們就會失去超能力
- Why? - So we can live human lives.
- 怎么會這樣？ - 這樣我們就能過凡人的生活
Love, connect...
去相愛，結合
...grow old, die.
慢慢變老，一起死去
What happened to us?
咱們發生過什么事？
Summer of 4 B.C.
公元前4年的夏天
We were becoming mortal, like now.
我們像現在一樣是凡人
They came after me with swords.
他們拿著劍追殺我
But you saved me.
是你救了我
1850.
1850年
They set our house on fire.
他們點著了咱們的房子
You pulled me out of the flames.
你把我從大火里拉了出來
Eighty years ago.
80年前呢
What happened then?
那時怎么了？
We were living in Miami...
我們住在邁阿密
...and a new movie was playing in town.
城里正上映新電影
Frankenstein.
《科學怪人》
And after...
散場以后
...we walked down Flagler Street...
咱們沿著大街走回家
...and you took my hand, and you held it so tight.
你那么緊地拉著我的手
And they attacked us in an alley.
一條小路上我們被人襲擊了
They hit you so hard. There was so much blood.
你被打得很重，流了那么多的血
They wouldn't let me ride in the ambulance with you.
醫生不讓我在救護車里陪你
And by the time I got to the hospital, you were awake.
等我赶到醫院，你已經醒了
But you didn't know me.
可你不認得我了
So I left.
我只能走了
Every time we're together...
每次我們聚到一起
...they come after you through me.
你都會因為我受傷
You're built to save people more than the rest of us.
你天生就比我們更能幫助他人
That's who you are. You're a hero.
這就是你，你是個英雄
The insurance policy of the gods.
你是眾神的守護者
Keep one alive. You.
我們就算剩下一個，也會是你
To protect this world.
來繼續保護這個世界
Mary!
瑪麗！
Mom!
媽媽！
- Mary! - Stay down!
- 瑪麗！ - 趴下
Okay.
好了
Mary?
瑪麗！
Stop.
別忙了
Oh, no! No! Please!
不，不要！
Stay down.
趴下
Hey! Mary!
嘿，瑪麗！
Let's go, get her up!
咱們走，扶她起來！
Come on, Chuck. Let's go, let's go.
堅持一下，咱們走
- Morphine. - Here. Help in here!
- 給我嗎啡 - 來這儿幫忙
Hold her down. Hold her down.
讓她別動
Hold her down.
按住她
- You want the monitor now? - Stay calm.
- 現在接上監控器？ - 冷靜點
- Hold her, hold her, hold her. - Need EKG leads.
- 把她按住了 - 給我心電圖設備探頭
Upon us all, Hancock.
你跟我們一樣，漢考克
You're no different.
照樣會死
Time to shut her down, Hancock.
是時候跟她做個了結了，漢考克
It's been a nice run.
跟你斗還挺有意思
Oh, we are all sincerely gonna miss you.
我們都會想念你的
But it is time for you to move on.
可你的死期到了
And maybe to a happier place.
沒准還能進天堂
You can thank me if you want to...
你要想謝我也行…
...superhero.
超級英雄
You didn't!
怎么又砍我手！
Aaron!
艾倫！
ONE MONTH LATER
（一個月后）
- What about Attila the Hun? - Completely cross-eyed.
- 匈奴王長什么樣？ - 是個斗雞眼
- Cross-eyed? - Yep.
- 斗雞眼？ - 嗯
All right, what about Queen Elizabeth?
那伊麗莎白女王呢？
- Needy. - J.F. K? What about him?
- 十分飢渴 - 肯尼迪呢？怎么死的？
Oh, yeah.
哦，這個
"Oh, yeah"? Anything more?
“這個”？沒別的了？
Not like that. I was in Cuba for the whole missile thing.
不是啊，當時我在古巴，正是導彈危机
Yeah, hang on.
等一下
- Hello? - Ray.
- 喂？ - 是瑞吧
Hey, I've been trying to call you.
我一直在給你打電話
Yeah, I was out of cell range.
嗯，我之前奔出服務區了
- Are you outside? - Yeah.
- 你在露天的地方嗎？ - 是啊
- Look up. - All right, I'm looking up.
- 抬頭看看 - 好的，我抬頭看看
I'm looking up.
我正抬頭看著呢
- Baby? - What?
- 寶貝？ - 怎么了？
You're gonna change the world.
你會改變世界的
- Good job, Ray. - Oh, my God, Ray.
- 瑞，干得不錯 - 我的天哪
Hey. Look up.
抬頭看吶
Hancock.
漢考克
I'm proud of you.
我為你驕傲
Thanks.
謝謝你
Will I get in trouble for that?
在那儿登廣告不會惹麻煩吧？
NOTE: small scene during the credits
（請稍會，還有一點情節）
- Freeze! - Don't move!
- 站住！ - 別動！
- Oh, my God! Sam! No! - Drop your weapon, sir!
- 天哪，我的薩姆！ - 放下武器！
Get back! Get back! Get back!
后退！后退！后退！
- Drop it! - Get back or I'll shoot! Get back!
- 放下槍 - 不后退我就開槍了
Get back! I'm not playing.
快后退，我沒開玩笑
Get back. Get back!
給我后退！
Damn, Handjob. Where you come from?
靠，汗烤雞，你從哪儿冒出來的？
All right, relax. Just tell me what you need.
別緊張，說說你的要求
Tell them cops to take their guns off of me.
告訴警察別拿槍對著我
- All right. - Tell them to take the guns off me.
- 好的 - 讓他們別瞄著我
Just take them off. Lower your weapons.
別瞄著他，先放下槍
You're gonna get us out of here with that tight-ass Wolverine outfit on.
你穿得跟金剛狼似的，先把我倆從這帶走
Now let's make it happen, asshole.
現在就做，混蛋！